ynot.com 2019-04-26

# YNOT | YNOT Privacy Policy

**YNOT Privacy Policy**  
_Last Modified: October 7, 2016_

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites (collectively, our “Services”) offered by YNOT Group, LLC or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies (collectively, “YNOT”). By using our Services and/or registering with YNOT, you acknowledge and accept the provisions in this Privacy Policy and grant YNOT permission to collect, store, and use the items of personal information described herein, so long as YNOT adheres to the standards set forth more clearly below.

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and provide such amendments to you by posting a revised version on our website. If the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with thirty (30) days’ notice prior to the effectiveness thereof by posting notice of the change in a prominent place on the YNOT website, such as presenting to you a click-through page immediately following your account login. Otherwise, in the case of insubstantial changes, the revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In any event, we will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most changes will be minor. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its Last Modified date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or by regular post mail at the following physical address:

Privacy Matters  
c/o YNOT Group, LLC  
PO BOX 922728  
Norcross, GA 30010  
USA

Information Collected

In order to provide our full range of Services, we may collect the following types of information:

Information you provide. When you register for a username, we ask you for personal information (such as your email address, time zone, and an account password). In order to improve the quality of our Services and to provide you with a better user experience, we may combine the information you submit with information provided by third parties.

Log information. Each time you access our Services, our servers may automatically record in their server logs information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol or “IP” address, the date and time of your request, browser type, browser language, and one or more cookies (see description below) that may uniquely identify your browser.

Links. YNOT may present links that include codes that enable us to track whether these links have been followed. This information is used to improve the quality of our advertising and customized content, as well as the organization and layout of our website.

Cookies. Assuming your browser is configured to accept them, when you visit our websites, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser. We may also set one or more cookies in your browser when you click on an ads or other links presented on our website. Cookies make it possible to store user preferences and record which portions of our website you and other users are using the most. We use cookies solely for the purpose of improving the quality of our Service.

User communications. We may retain communications that you send to YNOT by email or otherwise, in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our Services.

Affiliated YNOT Services on other sites. From time to time, we may offer some of our Services on or through other websites. In the event that we do offer such services, it is possible that personal information you provide to those sites may be sent to YNOT to facilitate delivery of those services. We will process such information under this Privacy Policy as if the information had been submitted directly from you to YNOT. Any affiliated site through which our Services are offered will likely have its own privacy policy, which may be very different from ours. It is very important for you to review the privacy policies for such affiliated sites before submitting personal information to them.

Other sites. This Privacy Policy only applies to Services offered by YNOT. We are not able to exercise control over sites that are linked to from within our various Services. These other sites may collect data, set their own cookies in your browser, or ask you to provide personal information.

Use of Personal Information

YNOT processes personal information only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the reasons set forth above, such purposes also include:

Providing our Services (which includes displaying customized advertising and other content); Auditing, research, and analysis (to maintain, protect, and improve our Services); Technical diagnostics (to ensure our network is functioning as expected); Protecting the rights or property of YNOT or our users, or third parties; Creating new Services; to send you email announcements (which may include newsletters, special offers or transnational details); and Marketing and sales of advertising.

YNOT processes personal information on our servers, which are located in the United States of America and in other countries. As a result, there exists the possibility that we may process your personal information on a server that is not located in your home country. In some cases, we may process personal information at the request of third parties and according to their instructions, such as our advertising partners. We will treat all personal information processed at the request of a third party exactly as if we had collected the processed personal information ourselves.

Privacy Principle: Choice

You may, if you wish, use some of our Services without registering for a username. However, when you sign up for our Services that require registration, we ask you to provide personal information, such as your email address. We will ask for your consent prior to using any provided personal information is any way that is different from the stated purpose for which that information was collected.

In the event that we develop a new use for personal information that is not described in this Privacy Policy, you will be given the opportunity to opt out of such use. We will not collect or use sensitive information, such as racial or ethnic origins, sexuality, politics, religion, or medical information, for any purpose not described herein.

You may configure your browser settings to prevent cookies from being stored on your computer or other browsing device. You should be aware, however, that some features of our Services might not function properly without cookies enabled.

Privacy Principle: Onward Transfer

YNOT may from time to time share personal information with individuals or other companies. In the event that we share information with companies or individuals not a part of YNOT, we will only do so in the following circumstances:

If we have asked for and received your consent.

For the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf, we may provide personal information to trusted persons or businesses. We will require these third-party processors to adopt appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Further, all third-party processors will be provided with a copy of this Privacy Policy and instructions that all processing of personal information must be done in accordance herewith.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of your personal information is reasonably necessary: (a) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (b) to enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; or (d) as required or permitted by law, to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of YNOT, its users, or the public.

This Privacy Policy may be superseded by an acquiring party’s policies in the event that YNOT becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who viewed a certain page in our website, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually.

Privacy Principle: Security

Appropriate security measures are taken to protect your personal information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction. These measures include internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices. Physical security measures are also taken to prevent unauthorized access to systems where your personal information is stored.

Your personal information is revealed to YNOT employees, contractors, and agents on a need-to-know basis in operating, developing, or improving our Services. As a condition of their employment or association with YNOT, these individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations. If they fail to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information, they may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution.

Privacy Principle: Data Integrity

YNOT processes personal information only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We review our data collection, storage, and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store, and process only that personal information which is needed to provide or improve our Services or as otherwise permitted hereunder. Although we depend on our users to keep their own personal information up to date, we also perform reasonable actions to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current.

Privacy Principle: Access

We make good-faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information that we have collected. In the event that such information is inaccurate, we will endeavor to provide facilities that allow you to either correct this data or to delete it, provided we are not otherwise required to retain such data by law or for legitimate business purposes. Before processing requests to access, delete, or alter such data, we ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, deleted, or corrected. We may refuse to process requests: (i) that require disproportionate technical effort; (ii) that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic; (iii) that would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes); (iv) that jeopardize the privacy of others; or (v) for which access is not otherwise required. Unless providing access and correction service would involve a disproportionate effort, we will perform it free of charge.

Privacy Principle: Enforcement

YNOT regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. If you feel there has been a specific instance where we have failed to comply with this Privacy Policy, please bring this matter to our attention by sending a detailed description of such noncompliance to the following physical address:

Privacy Matters  
c/o YNOT Group, LLC  
PO BOX 922728  
Norcross, GA 30010  
USA

It is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns when we receive formal written complaints at this address. In order to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between YNOT and an individual, we will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, such as local data protection authorities.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or by regular post mail at the following physical address:

Privacy Matters  
c/o YNOT Group, LLC  
PO BOX 922728  
Norcross, GA 30010  
USA
